export const chapter = "Chapter - 9: Determiner";
export const noOfActivities = 3;

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 1) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Tick the correct option:",
    questions: [
        {
          question: "What are Demonstrative Determiners?",
          optionA: "My, our, your",
          optionB: "This, that, these, those",
          optionC: "What, which, whose",
          correctAnswer: "B) This, that, these, those",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which type of determiners are used with singular countable nouns, based on the word immediately following them?",
          optionA: "Numerals",
          optionB: "Possessive Determiners",
          optionC: "Indefinite Articles",
          correctAnswer: "C) Indefinite Articles",
        },
        {
          question: "In which case is the article 'an' used?",
          optionA: "Before a noun beginning with a consonant sound",
          optionB: "Before a noun beginning with a vowel sound",
          optionC: "Before a proper noun",
          correctAnswer: "B) Before a noun beginning with a vowel sound",
        },
        {
          question:
            "When is the definite article 'the' used before a singular noun?",
          optionA:
            "To show a definite person or thing that has been mentioned before",
          optionB: "Before any singular noun",
          optionC: "Before a proper noun",
          correctAnswer:
            "A) To show a definite person or thing that has been mentioned before",
        },
        {
          question: "What do Numerals include?",
          optionA: "Demonstrative determiners",
          optionB: "Some, several, any, few, first, second, etc.",
          optionC: "My, our, your, her, his, its, their, etc.",
          correctAnswer: "B) Some, several, any, few, first, second, etc.",
        },
        {
          question: "In which case should articles be omitted?",
          optionA: "Before names of days and months",
          optionB: "Before most proper nouns",
          optionC: "Before names of games",
          correctAnswer: "B) Before most proper nouns",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What is the primary purpose of not using articles before the names of things or places?",
          optionA: "To indicate their primary function",
          optionB: "To make the sentence shorter",
          optionC: "It is a grammatical rule",
          correctAnswer: "A) To indicate their primary function",
        },
        {
          question:
            "When is 'the' used before the names of books, newspapers, and radio channels?",
          optionA: "Always",
          optionB: "Only for popular ones",
          optionC: "When they refer to specific ones",
          correctAnswer: "C) When they refer to specific ones",
        },
        {
          question: "In which case should 'an' be used instead of 'a'?",
          optionA: "Before a noun beginning with a vowel sound",
          optionB: "Before a noun beginning with a consonant sound",
          optionC: "Before proper nouns",
          correctAnswer: "A) Before a noun beginning with a vowel sound",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which of the following is an example of omission of articles based on determiners?",
          optionA: "The cotton of this area is fine.",
          optionB: "This is an apple. This is my apple.",
          optionC:
            "The minister is likely to call on the President of India today.",
          correctAnswer: "B) This is an apple. This is my apple.",
        },
      ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 2) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Fill in the blanks:",
    questions: [
        {
          question: "This television and that antenna are ___________.",
          optionA: "new",
          optionB: "old",
          optionC: "broken",
          correctAnswer: "a) new",
        },
        {
          question: "My father taught me to obey my elders and ___________.",
          optionA: "sisters",
          optionB: "teachers",
          optionC: "friends",
          correctAnswer: "b) teachers",
        },
        {
          question: "All students had to take ___________ mango each.",
          optionA: "one",
          optionB: "two",
          optionC: "three",
          correctAnswer: "a) one",
        },
        {
          question: "I am left with ___________ money.",
          optionA: "much",
          optionB: "little",
          optionC: "some",
          correctAnswer: "b) little",
        },
        {
          question: "___________ Ganga is the longest river in India.",
          optionA: "A",
          optionB: "An",
          optionC: "The",
          correctAnswer: "c) The",
        },
        {
          question: "Man doesn't live for ___________ alone.",
          optionA: "bread",
          optionB: "water",
          optionC: "air",
          correctAnswer: "a) bread",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The rocket is used to launch satellites into ___________ space.",
          optionA: "any",
          optionB: "some",
          optionC: "the",
          correctAnswer: "c) the",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Article 'a' is used with a noun beginning with a ___________ sound.",
          optionA: "vowel",
          optionB: "consonant",
          optionC: "silent",
          correctAnswer: "b) consonant",
        },
        {
          question: "Corruption must be rooted out from ___________ country.",
          optionA: "our",
          optionB: "the",
          optionC: "any",
          correctAnswer: "b) the",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which social reformer is credited with incorporating provisions for reservation in ___________ Constitution of India to uplift the Scheduled Castes?",
          optionA: "Sri Narayan Guru",
          optionB: "Periyar E.V. Ramaswamy",
          optionC: "Dr. Bhimrao Ramji Ambedkar",
          correctAnswer: "c) Dr. Bhimrao Ramji Ambedkar",
        },
      ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 3)
  activityData = {
    activity: "Write 'True' for True and 'False' for False statements:",
    questions: [
        {
          question:
            "The caste system in ancient India was based solely on family wealth.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Interrogative determiners include words like 'what,' 'which,' and 'whose.'",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Possessive determiners such as 'my,' 'our,' and 'your' are used with plural nouns.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question: "Numerals include words like 'some,' 'several,' and 'few.'",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question: "Articles are divided into three types: a, an, and the.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Abstract and material nouns always require the use of definite articles.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Omission of articles is acceptable when using determiners.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The caste system resulted in economic prosperity and national unity in ancient India.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question: "Continuous wars weakened the rulers of the warrior class.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The rise of nationalism was an important implication of the social reform movement.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
      ],
  };

export var activityData;
